

CONTACT ME AT

- Siborongborong
 North Sumatera
- evisilaban75@gmail.com
- 0822 30313728
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/e vi-rosalina-silaban-1943a9215

ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCES

- Secretary of Del Programming
 Club
- Coordinator of Division

 Administration in KPU Himasti
- Member of Division Data and
 Information in KPU BEM IT Del

AWARDS

- Certificate of Completion Mini School Web Developer Fundamental (Harisenin)
- Certificate of Graduation
 Learning to Create Front-End
 Web for Beginners
 (Diicoding.com)
- Certificate of Graduation
 Learning Web Programming
 Basic (Dicoding.com)
- Certificate of Graduation
 Learning React Navite Mobile
 App Development (Sanbercode)

EVI ROSALINA SILABAN

INFORMATICS STUDENTS

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am interested in web development and Quality Assurance with the simple experience I have. I have the desire to learn new technologies and feel comfortable working in teams, accepting challenges and assignment. I remain focused and dedicated to my work. I have good communication skills.

EDUCATION

Del Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Informatics | 2019 - Now

GPA: 3.28

EXPERIENCES

Student Teaching Assistant

Del Institute of Technology | Feb 2022 - Present

Help lecturers to provide practicum materials and provide tutorial classes on operating system courses

Front End Developer

Dimall | Marc 2022 - Present

Developing some pages on the Dimall website using the reactjs framework.

SKILLS SUMMARY

Technical Skill

HTML, CSS, JS, C, Java, PHP, MySQL

Tools/Editor

NetBeans, Eclipse, Postman, Visual Studio Code, Jira

Framework

Bootstrap, ReactJs, VueJs, Laravel, Selenium, Robot Framework, cucumber

PROJECTS

HIMASTI

Developing a static webiste by using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.

Covid-19

Developing a responsive website using HTML, CSS, Javascript.

Campflix

Simple movies website by using ReactJs and Public API.